<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Rx Homework</string>

    <string name="text">Those are the offices and these are the cubicles. That’s my cubicle there, and this is your cubicle. This is your phone.
        Never answer your phone. Let the Voicemail System answer it. This is your Voicemail System Manual. There are no personal phone calls allowed.
        We do, however, allow for emergencies. If you must make an emergency phone call, ask your supervisor first. If you can’t find your supervisor, ask Phillip Spiers,
        who sits over there. He’ll check with Clarissa Nicks, who sits over there. If you make an emergency phone call without asking, you may be let go.
        These are your in- and out-boxes. All the forms in your inbox must be logged in by the date shown in the upper- left- hand corner, initialed by you in
        the upper-right-hand corner, and distributed to the Processing Analyst whose name is numerically coded in the lower-left-hand corner.
        The lower-right-hand corner is left blank. Here’s your Processing Analyst Numerical Code Index. And here’s your Forms Processing Procedures Manual.
        You must pace your work. What do I mean? I’m glad you asked that. We pace our work according to the eight-hour workday. If you have twelve hours of work in
        your in-box, for example, you must compress that work into the eight-hour day. If you have one hour of work in your in-box, you must expand that work to
        fill the eight- hour day. That was a good question. Feel free to ask questions. Ask too many questions, however, and you may be let go.That is our receptionist.
        She is a temp. We go through receptionists here. They quit with alarming frequency. Be polite and civil to the temps. Learn their names, and invite them to lunch occasionally.
        But don’t get close to them, as it only makes it more difficult when they leave. And they always leave. You can be sure of that.The men’s room is over there.
        The women’s room is over there. John LaFountaine, who sits over there, uses the women’s room occasionally. He says it is accidental. We know better,
        but we let it pass. John LaFountaine is harmless, his forays into the forbidden territory of the women’s room simply a benign thrill, a faint blip on the dull,
        flat line of his life.Russell Nash, who sits in the cubicle to your left, is in love with Amanda Pierce, who sits in the cubicle to your right.
        They ride the same bus together after work. For Amanda Pierce, it is just a tedious bus ride made less tedious by the idle nattering of Russell Nash.
        But for Russell Nash, it is the highlight of his day. It is the highlight of his life. Russell Nash has put on forty pounds and grows fatter with each passing month,
        nibbling on chips and cookies while peeking glumly over the partitions at Amanda Pierce and gorging himself at home on cold pizza and ice cream while watching adultvideos on TV.</string>
</resources>